Brin Bliss

brinmbliss@gmail.com 858.703.7142 Pittsburgh Area

SKILLS

Programs: Microsoft Office (especially Word and Excel), Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Sketch, InVision, Balsamiq

Languages: Javascript, HTML/CSS

Other: Information gathering, collating and synthesizing research, taking direction, organization, handling details, delivering feedback, identifying and rectifying problems, managing conflict, punctuality, social media, public speaking, copywriting and editing

ABOUT ME

Detail fanatic, lifelong learner, and research enthusiast. I love finding out new things (and telling everyone I know). I also love teaching, writing, science, and art. One of the best feelings in the world is finally finding an answer twenty articles into a link chain. It is the closest I will ever get to being Sherlock Holmes, unless I finally go in for a deerstalker.

EXPERIENCE

Test Analyst - Q Analysts onsite at Facebook 2017-2018

- Managed a team of 5-6 individuals in triage for the Oculus Go dogfooding effort
- Researched known issues, new issues, and general software specifications in order to prioritize and route test reports
- Moderated group of ~500 people that oversaw feedback and tech support for company dogfooders
- Created and led initial framework for large-scale hardware dogfooding at Oculus

Test Prep Tutor – Compass Education Group 2017-2018

- Produced and presented lessons to aid students preparing for the verbal portions of the ACT and SAT
- Monitored progress and adjusted lessons accordingly

Corporate and Community Intern – Make-A-Wish Utah 2016

- Collected information on local corporations for fundraising purposes
- Cultivate relationship with previous donors

Undergraduate Research Assistant - Dr. Gary Burlingame 2014

- Gathered research from various sources to support a meta-analysis
- Located electronic and hard copies of research as part of a group of 8 individuals

Research Assistant - Brigham Young University 2014-2015

- Performed phone survey of colleges across the US
- Coded and analyzed responses

Social Media Assistant - NavigateHCR 2015-2016

- Wrote and published weekly social media posts across 3 company accounts
- Completed other tasks as needed, including research and analysis

EDUCATION

Brigham Young University – Psychology B.S. – 2016 **Bloc** – Designer Track - 2017